last 5 minutes
Teacher I need a new answer card
Not much time left
OK, stop writing
Put your hands on your head
Students in the last row help collect answer cards
[No. 20 Yu Seqi]
[No. 15 Liu Jieyi]
[1st place Cui Jing]
Xiaojing did not disappoint the teacher
Now there is no problem with my grades in school
Just perform well during the interview
I will definitely be admitted to the Department of Medicine of a Korean University
Congratulations Cui Jing
It’s true that strength cannot be hidden
With this result, you better not have any illusions
Department of Medicine, Korea University?
Don’t you have to get a scholarship?
Harp section of the Department of Music, Korea University
We only accept one student per year, you know?
Are you sure you want to apply?
Jai, this is not up to your standards.
Did you fill in the wrong answer card?
Does your sister's incident make you very sad?
The teacher can understand
But there's still a chance
Concentrate on preparing for the university entrance exam
[Transcript]
Dad, I'm sorry
I...want to ask you something
I also want to be like my sister
I need "Devil-level questions"
["Good-natured Competition"]
Auntie, you bought a new car
Yes
Because…
The evidence that was originally placed here
where did you take it
Already reconciled
I'm tired
I don’t want to be disappointed in your father anymore.
Didn’t you do it for money from the beginning?
Who do you think will suffer more between the two of us?
Also
Who am I to say this?
Yes, it’s really not easy to make progress in your senior year of high school.
What congratulations? No need.
Oh my God, really?
Do you still have the hiking clothes you bought last time?
Put it on quickly
Hurry up
Now?
Almost there
[Registration for the 100-day prayer for the University Entrance Examination is open]
Come here quickly
Is it enough for us to earn bit by bit like this?
There will be a big exam in 100 days
I don’t know if it’s because I didn’t eat this.
Everyone did very poorly in this final exam.
Really?
Is this the case with Yu Seqi?
I don’t know if she has made it into the top 20 in the school.
So who is number one in the school this time?
There is…
My name is Cui Jing
The sweet baby I gave patches to on her school anniversary
Hello
Mama-san calls you over
Me?
[Liu Jiena]
are you okay
Did you fight to this extent?
Did you just get first place in the school?
It's amazing
But compared to being ranked first in the school
The harder thing is to maintain it, right?
Look at Seulgi
If I didn’t eat this, my grades would drop right away.
Seulgi…
It turns out that I got first place by taking medicine.
There are only a few days left for the big exam
Take it
Think of it as my gift to you
Open it and take a look
I heard today is your birthday
Then you are not underage, right?
There is a regular customer in our store
seems to be very interested in you
I can lend you money to help you with your living expenses and tuition fees
But you also have to pay something
give me that
I don't want to
Go ahead and sue me
I don't want to either
I want to make a suggestion
Although I don’t know how you convinced Auntie
But that doesn't work for me
Demon king level questions
The devil-level questions for this big exam
I can get it for you
What's going on
Damn it
[The ledger is here. Thank you very much.
Come to the top floor]
This is the 112 emergency reporting center
I want to report something
sorry
I was wrong. I'm really sorry.
Sorry, I'll call you later.
I have something to say to Liu Jieyi
But she never answered the phone
you can help me
talk to me
Was this place bugged by your dad too?
Or is he looking at us?
I have something to say
I have nothing nice to say
Your dad said he would give me devil-level questions
It seems that this matter is not in your plan
Shouldn't you...
Tell him you don't need it
Why why did I say that?
At least give me a reason
How would I know if you didn't say anything?
What are you thinking about? What are you planning?
how would i know
You seem to come home very late lately
I go swimming
You are right. After you really move your body,
Concentration has improved
Blow dry your hair before going to bed. If you catch a cold, you'll be in trouble.
Dad, you don’t really want to give it to Seulgi
Demon king level questions
do you care
You don’t want two to be number one in the country, right?
She seems ambitious
She would be a good front runner
leader
Are you afraid that I will reveal your secret?
But compared to me...
It might be more dangerous
Aren't you worried?
The university entrance exam is her only
A way to change your destiny
"Dead Father" and "Devil-level Question"
Which one is more valuable to her
She is not as innocent as you think
Well, since we have to do it, why not do it more thoroughly?
Lest she regret it later
How about letting her talk about it herself?
Collect evidence by the way
[100 days before the university entrance exam]
Being part of a "team"
You should also show some sincerity, right?
[Park Myung-ho, University Entrance Examination Question Setting Committee]
National University Professor Salary…
It actually allows him to collect art
You don't need to think about it to know what's going on.
Hello Professor
hello
Oh
what is your intention
[Korea University Department of Medicine Interview Examination Room]
Li Xialin
Finished
Hey, be quiet
what is this sound
Where is the moaning coming from?
Did a cat in heat come in?
What the hell? Does she think this is her home?
Really sick
Cui Jing
Sorry, please wait a moment
Everyone, grab the registration form and be sure to return it today.
[Countdown to 92 days]
What else do you want from me?
[Countdown to 70 days]
Strange, why is it 92 days?
[Admission results]
[Not Admitted]
[Daejundong Valet Delivery Service]
[Looking for the "Hotel Goddess" of Caihua Girls' High School]
[Who]
[Isn't "Bar Goddess" just a beautiful escort girl?]
This damn girl...
What are you doing?
Give me back
Why? Do you think the money is too little?
I can give it to you again
do you really want this
Go back
What kind of moral saint are you pretending to be?
You don't work in a hotel yet
Damn what did you say
I haven't done it a long time ago
See you smiling so happily when you got the business card
I knew it
Also
I’ve been exposed to it since childhood, so of course I would do that kind of thing
are you crazy
Hey, is it you?
Is it you who posted on the discussion board?
Do you think I am you?
Make a living by digging out other people's secrets
Hello…
Hello
let me go
Don't try to win Jay's exam
I want to continue to have private tutoring at Jie Yi’s house.
You better watch your mouth
Damn it
what are you talking about
[Video Clip Subtitles Last Cut Pro X]
you have a cold
No, it's allergy
Whose things fell off...
why did you come
Do you have a dog at home?
So what
Mom, take care of it
Sometimes I imagine Jieyin dying
If it really dies later
I might be too sad
So rehearse it in your mind first
i don't know anything
But Jay said the conditions for me to join the secret tutoring program
Just adopt Jieyin
Really, that's it
Jay